Preliminary Guide to the Social Democrats, USA Records, 1937-1994 (Bulk 1970-1994)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 2001-0079
  - contents of Box 11: (Box 11)
    - 1989 Debs Dinner, John Sweeny
      - Hotel / Party (Box 11)
      - Printed Material (Box 11)
      - Seating Plans (Box 11)
  - contents of Box 12: (Box 12)
    - 1989 Debs Dinner, John J Sweeny, (two folders) (Box 12)
    - Country Files
      - Togo (Box 12)
      - Tunisia (Box 12)
      - Turkey, (three folders) (Box 12)
      - Ukraine (Box 12)
      - Uruguay (Box 12)
      - U.S.S.R. (Box 12)
      - Venezuela
        - Venezuela 1993 (Box 12)
        - Venezuela, (four folders) (Box 12)
        - Venezuela, File 2 (Box 12)
      - Spanish Sahara (Box 12)
      - Sudan (Box 12)
      - Surinam (Box 12)
      - Sweden
        - Sweden 1993 (Box 12)
        - Sweden, (three folders) (Box 12)
        - Sweden, file 2, (two folders) (Box 12)
        - Sweden, file 3 (Box 12)
        - Human Environment (Box 12)
        - Political Life (Box 12)
        - Working Life (Box 12)
    - Switzerland (Box 12)
    - Syria (Box 12)
    - Thailand (Box 12)
    - Tibet (Box 12)
    - Soviet Union
      - Soviet Union, file 2 (Box 12)
      - Soviet Union, file 3 (Box 12)
      - Soviet Union, file 4 (Box 12)
      - Soviet Union, 1991 August Coup (Box 12)
  - contents of Box 13: (Box 13)
    Reformat newspaper clippings.
    - Pioneer Valley Local, 1979, (three folders) (Box 13)
    - Pioneer Valley, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Michael Perry (Box 13)
    - Persian Gulf Crisis Resolution and Cover Letter (Box 13)
    - Dave Peterson (Box 13)
    - Pioneeer Valley Local 1973-1978, (three folders) (Box 13)
    - Charles Perkel (Box 13)
    - Scabs Renamed Permanent Replacements 1990 December (Box 13)
    - Permanent Replacements Issue Paper: Extra Copies and Letters From Congressman Rangel (Box 13)
    - New America Fund Appeal 1982 (Box 13)
    - New America Fund Appeal 1983 (Box 13)
    - New America Fund Letter, (three folders) (Box 13)
    - Ron Moore (Box 13)
    - Stephen Morris (Box 13)
    - Moscow Olympics, (two folders) (Box 13)
    - Douglas Payne, (three folders) (Box 13)
    - Cleo Paturis (Box 13)
    - New Members letters and forms (Box 13)
    - New Left (Box 13)
    - New America Letter (Box 13)
    - New Jersey Organizing Plans 1973 (Box 13)
    - YSD National Convention 1980 (Box 13)
    - New Pepublic Ad (Poland) (Box 13)
    - The New Socialist 1973 (Box 13)
    - Jennifer O'Dell (Box 13)
    - Organization Committee (Box 13)
    - Bios, articles, New Moment Conf., 1991 November 5-10 (Box 13)
    - "A New Moment In America?" Post-Conference follow-up (Box 13)
    - New Member Committee (Box 13)
    - New Members 1992 (Box 13)
    - The New Republic (Box 13)
    - Organizational Conference (Box 13)
    - National Strategy Infomation Center, Inc., (two folders) (Box 13)
    - The National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation Inc. (Box 13)
    - National Lawyers Guild (Box 13)
    - National Labor Relations Board (Box 13)
  - contents of Box 14: (Box 14)
    - National Labor Federation, (three folders) (Box 14)
    - Mihajlo Mihajlov, (three folders) (Box 14)
    - Morris Milgram (Box 14)
    - Miller, Bruce (Box 14)
    - Tom Milstein (Box 14)
    - MODTLE: Mobilization on Development, Trade, Labor and the Environment (Box 14)
    - Socialist International Committee on Economic Policy (Box 14)
    - Socialist International Committee on Environment (Box 14)
    - Socialist International Committee on Human Rights (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee Meeting, Latin America and the Caribbean, Kingston, Jammica, 1989 May 30-31 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Basel, Switzerland 1982 November 3-4, (three folders) (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Brussels, Belgium 1983 November 24-25 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Oslo, Norway, 1983 February 3 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Basle, 1982 November 3-4 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Caracas, Venezuela, 1984 February 25-March 2 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Slangerup, Denmark, 1984 April 24-26, (three folders) (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Bornmersvik, Sweden, 1985 June 18-19 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Rio De Janeiro, Brazil, 1984 October 1-2 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Vienna, Austria, 1985 October 15-16 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting, Lima, Peru, 1986 (Box 14)
    - SI: Bureau Meeting Minutes, 1975, (three folders) (Box 14)
    - SI Committee: Latin America and Caribbean, Santo Domigo, 1988 November 26-27 (Box 14)
    - SI comittee in The Latin America and the Caribbean, Rio De Jameiro, 1988 April 29-30 (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee in Latin America and the Caribbean, SICLAC, Caracas, Venezuela, 1987 December 8-9 (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee for the Defense of the Revolution in Nicaragua, Managua, 1981 June 25 (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee on Disarmament and Arms Control, SIDAC (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee on Economic Policy, SICEP, Lima, Peru, 1986 June 17-18 (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee on Economic Policy, SICEP, Vienna, Austria, 1985 October 14 (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee on Economic Policies, (two folders) (Box 14)
    - SI: China (Box 14)
    - SI: Committee, (two folders) (Box 14)
  - contents of Box 15: (Box 15)
    Reformat newspaper clippings and coated paper.
    - SI: Committee for the Defense of the Revolution in Nicaragua, Madrid, 1981 November 27 (Box 15)
    - SI: Nicaragua Observer Mission, 1990 February 25 (elections) (Box 15)
    - SI: ICFTU Conference on Central America, Guatemala, 1990 February 20-21 (Box 15)
    - SI: Calender, (two folders) (Box 15)
    - SI: Calender of Events, 1982 (Box 15)
    - SI: Central America (Box 15)
    - SI: Chile Committee, Santigo, Chile, 1988 July 2-3, (two folders) (Box 15)
    - SI: Chile Committee (Box 15)
    - SI: Chile (Box 15)
    - SI: Chile Mission, 1989 December 12-15 (Box 15)
    - SI: Circulars, (two folders) (Box 15)
    - South Africa, (ten folders) (Box 15)
    - Portugal, 1992 (Box 15)
    - Portugal (Box 15)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 15)
    - Russia, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Romania (Box 15)
    - Salvador, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Santa Domingo (Box 15)
    - San Marino (Box 15)
    - Seafarers (Box 15)
    - Saudi Arabia (Box 15)
    - Senegal (Box 15)
    - Singapore (Box 15)
    - SI: Leaders Meeting, Amsterdam (Box 15)
    - SI: Meetings, 1983 (Box 15)
    - SI: Meeting in Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic, 1984 February 22-24 (Box 15)
    - SI: Leader's Meeting in Caracas, Venezuela, 1982 February 24-25 (Box 15)
    - SI: Luncheon, 1971 June 29 (Box 15)
    - SI: Meeting in Caracas, 1982 (Box 15)
    - SI: Leaders Meeting, Vienna, Austria, 1989 March 9-10 (Box 15)
    - SI: Meeting of the Praesidium Bonn, 1981 July 15-16 (Box 15)
    - SI: Meeting Notices (Box 15)
    - SI: Membership, 1974, (two folders) (Box 15)
  - contents of Box 16: (Box 16)
    - National Convention 1990
      - Social Democrats, apportionment 1990 March 23-1990 March 25 (Box 16)
      - National Convention 1990 March 23-1990 March 25general-correspondence-speeches, (two folders) (Box 16)
      - Delegate Nominations MAL (Box 16)
      - Delegates (Box 16)
      - Printed material, (three folders) (Box 16)
      - Contributions (Box 16)
      - Local Elections (Box 16)
      - Pledge Plan Drive (Box 16)
      - NC Pre-Meeting (Box 16)
      - NC Post-Meeting (Box 16)
      - Delegate Elections MAL (Box 16)
      - Guests (Box 16)
      - Travel Subsidies (Box 16)
      - Apportionment (Box 16)
      - Greetings (Box 16)
      - Members-Observers (Box 16)
      - Finances (Box 16)
      - Contacts-Lists-Press (Box 16)
      - Hotel arrangements (Box 16)
      - Committees (Box 16)
      - National Committee (Box 16)
      - Nonmembers-Observers, (two folders) (Box 16)
      - Resolutions/Policy Statements, (Three folders) (Box 16)
      - Publicity, (Two folders (Box 16)
      - Convention Planning Committee for 1990 Convention (Box 16)
      - Daily Reports (Box 16)
    - National Convention 1994
      - Publicity (Box 16)
      - NC Post-Meeting (Box 16)
      - Lunch-Evie Dubrow (Box 16)
      - NC Pre-Meeting (Box 16)
      - National Committee-Proposed (Box 16)
      - YSD Convention (Box 16)
      - General Correspondence Speeches (Box 16)
      - Speakers (Box 16)
      - Committees (Box 16)
      - NAC-National Advisory Council (Box 16)
      - Convention List, (two folders) (Box 16)
      - NCA-National Committee Alternate (Box 16)
      - Greetings (Box 16)
      - Scripts/Bios. (Box 16)
      - Finances (Box 16)
      - Convention Rules (Box 16)
      - Convention Committee (Box 16)
      - Award (Box 16)
      - Contact-Lists-Press (Box 16)
  - contents of Box 17: (Box 17)
    - Grant Proposal Correspondence (Box 17)
    - Harry Goldberg (Box 17)
    - Roy Godson (Box 17)
    - Joe Godson (Box 17)
    - Glotzer, Al, (two folders) (Box 17)
    - Albert Glotzer (Box 17)
    - James Glaser (Box 17)
    - Robert Gilmore (Box 17)
    - Gene Glaberman (Box 17)
    - Chris Gersten (Box 17)
    - Grenada (Box 17)
    - Foundation for Human Rights and Democracy in China (Box 17)
    - Gates, Henry Louis, 1993 (Box 17)
    - García López, Antonio (Box 17)
    - Gay Rights, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Germinal Film (Box 17)
    - Carl Gershman
      - Writing (Box 17)
      - Biography (Box 17)
      - Why I am not a Conservative (Box 17)
    - The Heritage Foundation (Box 17)
    - Huber Matos (Box 17)
    - Human Rights Coalition, (three folders) (Box 17)
    - Steve High (Box 17)
    - Hess Boycott (Box 17)
    - Historians of American Communism (Box 17)
    - Vaclav Holesovsky (Box 17)
    - Homeless (Box 17)
    - Hyden, Tom (Box 17)
    - Health Care (Box 17)
    - Al Heaps (Box 17)
    - Steven D. Heller (Box 17)
    - Ambassador Gerald Hellman (Box 17)
    - Lillian Hellman (Box 17)
    - Helsinki Agreement Ad 1975 (Box 17)
    - Helsinki Agreement (Box 17)
    - Michael Harrington, (three folders) (Box 17)
    - Harrington- Gershman debate (Box 17)
    - Gun Control (Box 17)
    - Feliks Gross (Box 17)
    - Histadrut and its related organizations in the U.S., (four folders) (Box 17)
    - International Ladies Garmet Workers Union #1, (four folders) (Box 17)
    - International Ladies Garmet Workers Union #2 (Box 17)
    - Charles Gati (Box 17)
  - contents of Box 18: (Box 18)
    - National Convention March 1994
      - Credo/Resolutions/Policy Statement (Box 18)
      - Pledge Plan Drive (Box 18)
      - NC National Committee (Box 18)
      - Contributions (Box 18)
      - Printed Material (Box 18)
      - Non-member Observers (Box 18)
      - Members (Box 18)
    - Labor Research Association (Box 18)
    - Labor and Society (Box 18)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, LID
      - LID 1992-1993 (Box 18)
      - LID 1983 (Box 18)
      - LID through 1980, (five folders) (Box 18)
    - Grenada #1, (five folders) (Box 18)
    - Universities
      - Columbia, (two folders) (Box 18)
      - American (Box 18)
      - Albany (Box 18)
      - Minnesota (Box 18)
      - New York (Box 18)
      - Philadelphia (Box 18)
      - Reed (Box 18)
      - Tufts (Box 18)
      - Pennsylvania (Box 18)
      - Yale (Box 18)
      - UNC-Charlotte (Box 18)
      - Washington, D.C. (Box 18)
      - Binghampton (Box 18)
      - Cornell (Box 18)
      - ERAU (Box 18)
      - Evergreen (Box 18)
      - George Washington (Box 18)
      - Harvard (Box 18)
      - Indiana (Box 18)
      - Macalester (Box 18)
      - Michigan (Box 18)
    - Herman, Roger, NY Visit, 1984 February 7-10 (Box 18)
    - 1983 Institute Sperryville (Box 18)
    - IYY (Box 18)
    - Robert Leiken (Box 18)
    - Sam Leiken (Box 18)
    - Louise Leopold (Box 18)
    - George Lerski (Box 18)
    - Letters to the Editor (Box 18)
  - contents of Box 19: (Box 19)
    - Seymour Martin Lipset (Box 19)
    - Harry Lerner (Box 19)
    - Levenstien, Aaron (Box 19)
    - Libro libre (Box 19)
    - Herbert I. London (Box 19)
    - Glenn C. Loury (Box 19)
    - Lovestone, Jay (Box 19)
    - 1983 YPSL Journal (Box 19)
    - Benefit Contributors (Box 19)
    - Benefit Finances (Box 19)
    - 1983 Benefit Skit (Box 19)
    - 1983 YPSL Benefit (Box 19)
    - Bills from Social Democrats (Box 19)
    - June 1982 (Box 19)
    - Campus Coalition for Democracy (Box 19)
    - ANA
      - ANA Correspondence (Box 19)
      - ANA Distribution List (Box 19)
      - ANA Board of Elections (New York State) (Box 19)
      - ANA Bills Paid (Box 19)
      - ANA Bills (Box 19)
      - ANA Bank (Box 19)
      - ANA Flyers (Box 19)
      - ANA Flyers in Progress (Box 19)
      - ANA Fundraising (Box 19)
      - ANA Miscellaneous (Box 19)
      - ANA White Paper (Box 19)
      - ANA Proposals (Box 19)
      - ANA Positions (Box 19)
    - Ballots, National Selection (Box 19)
    - Articles on Social Democracy, AFL-CIO (Box 19)
    - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
    - April 1983, (two folders) (Box 19)
    - May 1983, (three folders) (Box 19)
    - Guillen Tour (Box 19)
    - Guillen Tour--Press (Box 19)
    - Dube (Box 19)
    - September 1982, (two folders) (Box 19)
    - Israel-Lebanon Peace Negotiations (Box 19)
    - Election Positions, June 1983, (two folders) (Box 19)
    - Flyers (Box 19)
    - YSD Financial Report, January 1983-January 1984 (Box 19)
    - International Contacts (Box 19)
    - Internal Projects (Box 19)
    - YIPME-The PLO in Lebanon (Box 19)
    - Mondale Campaign Activities (Box 19)
    - International Youth Conference (Box 19)
    - Mondale Campaign Position Papers (Box 19)
    - YIPME Leaflet, (three folders) (Box 19)
    - NEC (Box 19)
    - NEC Meeting (Box 19)
    - NSIC (Box 19)
    - NOTES (Box 19)
    - Randolph Bureau (Box 19)
    - Recipts (Box 19)
    - Recruitment (Box 19)
    - Request for Information (Box 19)
    - Middlebury (Box 19)
    - South Africa Conference, APRI (Box 19)
    - Speakers List (Box 19)
    - US Youth Council, Trip Reports (Box 19)
    - Eric Chenoweth, Delagate at Large (Box 19)
    - USYC Visiting Delegation (Box 19)
    - Convention Speeches (Box 19)
  - contents of Box 20: (Box 20)
    - SI: Membership, 1975 (Box 20)
    - SI: Mission, Chile, 1986 October 9-12 (Box 20)
    - SI: Working Group on the Middle East (Box 20)
    - SI: Middle East Mission Report, 1977 July 10, (two folders) (Box 20)
    - SI: Middle East Committee (Box 20)
    - SI: Middle East Roundtable, Vienna, 1978 February 12 (Box 20)
    - SI: Nicaragua (Box 20)
    - SI: Nicaragua Mission, 1990 January 12-14 (Box 20)
    - SEIU, World Bank Campaign (Box 20)
    - SI: Women (Box 20)
    - SI: Women, Non-governmental Organization (NGO), 1989 September 13-15 (Box 20)
    - SI: Women Correspondence (Box 20)
    - SI: Global Challenge (Box 20)
    - SI: Grenada (Box 20)
    - SI: Haiti (Box 20)
    - SI: Helsinki (Box 20)
    - SI: Human Rights (Box 20)
    - SI: Human Rights Conference (Box 20)
    - SI: ICFTU peace and Democracy Central America, El Salvador, 1989 February 11-12 (Box 20)
    - SI: International Council of Social Democratic Women, Helsinki, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
    - SI: International Council of Social Democratic Women, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - SI: International Falcon Movement (SI Children's Organization) (Box 20)
    - SI: International Falcon Movement, (two folders) (Box 20)
    - SI: International Council of Social Democratic Women, (three folders) (Box 20)
    - SI: International Union of Social Democratic Teachers (Box 20)
    - SI: International Union of Social Democratic Youth (Box 20)
    - SI: Committee for Latin America and the Caribbean Quito, Ecuador, 1990 January 17-18, (three folders) (Box 20)
    - SI: Latin America (Box 20)
    - SI: Kreisky-Arafat Meeting, 1979 July (Box 20)
    - SI: Leaders Meeting in Sheffield, U.K., 1984 June 20-21 (Box 20)
    - SI: Committee on Economic Policy, Sicep-Brussels, Belgium, 1985 April 16 (Box 20)
    - South Korea (Box 20)
    - South Pacific, (two folders) (Box 20)
    - South Yemen (Box 20)
    - Soviet Union (Box 20)
    - To Build a Better World: the 1962 socialist Platform (SP) (Box 20)
    - Solidarnosc Bulletin, 1983 January (Box 20)
    - Solidarnosc Bulletin, 1982 August (Box 20)
    - The Struggle for Democracy in Central America (Box 20)
    - El Slavador: Peaceful Revolution or Armed Struggle? (Box 20)
    - South Africa: Is Peaceful Change Possible? (Box 20)
    - Castro, Israel and the PLO (Box 20)
  - contents of Box 21: (Box 21)
    - Socialist Currents (Box 21)
    - Socialist Party Report, by Joan Suall (Box 21)
    - A Socialist Program for the Seventies (SP 1970) (Box 21)
    - Socialist Party, USA, late 1960s-early 1970s (Box 21)
    - The Nobel Lecture by Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn (Box 21)
    - Nixon Economics, 1970(SP) (Box 21)
    - Platform, 1956(SP) (Box 21)
    - Social Democracy of U.S. labor, by Corlgersman (SD, USA, 1978) (Box 21)
    - Social Democrats, USA (Box 21)
    - Socialism's New Beginning, By James D'Neal (SP,SDF, late 1950s) (Box 21)
    - Expanding Economic Democracy, by John Joyce (Box 21)
    - Social Democrats, USA, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Social Democrats, USA, 1975 (Box 21)
    - The Social Democratic Prospect, by Sidney Hook (SD, USA, 1976) (Box 21)
    - Solidarnosc Bulletin, 1981 October (Box 21)
    - Solidarnosc Bulletin, 1982 March (Box 21)
    - A Democratic Foreign Policy (Box 21)
    - Freedom As a Foreign Policy Base, by Wattenberg (NYTimes, 1976 July 13) (Box 21)
      and accompanying letters
    - Socialism: the Diamond, Not the Dung (Box 21)
    - Homelessness: an American Disgrace in two Dimensions (Box 21)
    - The Social Democrats, 1989 Fall, Debs Dinner Speeches (Box 21)
    - The Social Democrats, 1981 Spring, Debs Dinner Speeches (Box 21)
    - Organizing the Unorganized, Issue Paper, 1988 April (Box 21)
    - Receipt Speech, Social Democrat, 1990 Winter (Box 21)
    - The Social Democrat and Some Letters, 1992 January (Box 21)
    - Mobilization, April 25, (three folders) (Box 21)
    - The Social Democrats, 1988 (Box 21)
    - State of Principles (Box 21)
    - Union and Conspiracy Theory, 1989 January (Box 21)
    - Industry Homework, 1989 February (Box 21)
    - Corporate Takeovers, 1989 February (Box 21)
    - The Social Democrat, 1991 March (Box 21)
    - The Health Care Gap, 1989 Spring (Box 21)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith, 1979, (three folders) (Box 21)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith, 1993, (two folders) (Box 21)
    - Rolando Alum, Jr. (Box 21)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1980-1981, (two folders) (Box 21)
    - SI: Meeting of the Council, Dakar Sengal, 1987 October 15-16 (Box 21)
    - SI: International Council (Rome), 1987 April 8-9 (Box 21)
    - SI Council, Geneva, 1989 November 22-25, (two folders) (Box 21)
  - contents of Box 22: (Box 22)
    - Frontlash, (two folders) (Box 22)
    - Democratic Party Platform Committee Hearings (Box 22)
    - Healthcare Workers Strike; Youth Statement (Box 22)
    - YSD Convention 1984 Flyers (Box 22)
    - YSD Convention 1984, Correspondence, Fundraising (Box 22)
    - YSD Convention 1984, Resolutions as amended by the Convention (Box 22)
    - Convention and Recipts (Box 22)
    - Foreign Policy Conference Attendance (Box 22)
    - Transcripts; Dem. Solidarity Conference (Box 22)
    - Foreign Policy Conference Registration (Box 22)
    - Foreign Policy Conference Proposals/Programs (Box 22)
    - Correspondence (Box 22)
    - Coors Boycott (Box 22)
    - Film Series, (two folders) (Box 22)
    - Freedom Federation (Box 22)
    - Building on the Past for the Future (Box 22)
    - Fundraising (Box 22)
    - ILG/Imports (Box 22)
    - Foreign Policy Correspondence (ctd.), (two folders) (Box 22)
    - Foreign Policy Conference Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Foreign Policy Institute Site/Budget (Box 22)
    - Fundraising/Summer, Appeal to Members (Box 22)
    - Foreign Policy Conference, Finances (Box 22)
    - Conference Transcripts, (two folders) (Box 22)
    - New Members (Box 22)
    - YSD Bulletin (Box 22)
    - Articles on SD, AFL-CIO (Box 22)
    - New York Local (Box 22)
    - Washington Local (Box 22)
    - Reed College (Box 22)
    - NEC Meeting 1986 January 18 (Box 22)
    - 1987 Finances (Box 22)
    - Video Project (Box 22)
    - Wallenberg Intern Project (Box 22)
    - YEI (Box 22)
    - YIPME (Box 22)
    - YSD Activity Update (Box 22)
    - Appeal to Reason (Box 22)
    - Benefit
      - Activity Update for Trade Union Mailing (Box 22)
      - Finances (Box 22)
      - Journal (Box 22)
      - Scheduling, Miscellaneous (Box 22)
      - Advertisements (Box 22)
      - Correspondence (Box 22)
      - Flyers (Box 22)
    - YSD
      - Bulletin, 1984 August-1984 September (Box 22)
      - Bulletin, 1984 October-1984 November (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Resolutions as submitted to the Resolutions Committee (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Cruz/ Manglapus (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Scheduling (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Recruitment, Trasportation, Housing (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Registration (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Cruz/ Manglapus Reception, Recruitment (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Mailing Lists (Box 22)
      - Convention, 1984, Notes (Box 22)
    - Costa Rica, (two folders) (Box 22)
    - Social Democrats, New Members (Box 22)
    - Industrial Competitiveness (Box 22)
    - Democratic-Labor Project 1991 (Box 22)
    - TDU ( Don Slaiman) (Box 22)
  - contents of Box 23: (Box 23)
    - Speech (Box 23)
    - SD-Attacks on (Box 23)
    - SD Seminar, (two folders) (Box 23)
    - Democratic Labor Project, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Democratic-Labor Project, 1990 (Box 23)
    - Bill Clinton Endorsement (Box 23)
    - Address List of the Socialist International (Box 23)
    - Mineworkers (Box 23)
    - Labor-Democrats Project (Box 23)
    - Democratic/Labor Project 1988 (Box 23)
    - SI Congress NYC (Box 23)
    - 1996 Correspondence SDUSA (Box 23)
    - IP-Other Unions (Box 23)
    - Fund Appeals 1992, (two folders) (Box 23)
    - Apparent 1993 (Box 23)
    - A New Moment in America? A Washington Conversation on Politics and Culture (Box 23)
    - Social Democrats (Box 23)
    - Labor Management Cooperation, (five folders) (Box 23)
    - Is Russia a Socialist Community? A debate Between Earl Browdert and Max Schactman 1950 (Box 23)
    - Fall Notes: Original (Box 23)
    - Fall 1996 Notes: Working Draft (Box 23)
    - Clips of Review of The Remedy (Box 23)
    - Dues Billing 1981-1992, (two folders) (Box 23)
    - SD Issues Paper 1996 (Box 23)
    - 1982 Activity update (Box 23)
    - Democratic/Labor Project 1992 (Box 23)
    - III Congress of the Social Democracy of the Republic of Poland (Box 23)
    - June 24 NC Meeting (Box 23)
    - Issue Paper (Box 23)
    - Worker/Management Relation: Workplace of Future (Box 23)
    - 1992 Encyclical Seminars (Box 23)
    - Jobs Debate (Box 23)
    - Returned/Corrected copies of Encyclical (Box 23)
    - CREDO Seminars (Box 23)
    - Papal Encyclical 1992 March-25 (Box 23)
    - Encyclical Seminars Drafts (Box 23)
  - contents of Box 24: (Box 24)
    - Socialist International, General Conference, (two folders) (Box 24)
    - SI: Employment Policies Working Group (Box 24)
    - SI: Finance and General Purposes Committee (Box 24)
    - SI: Finance and Administration Committee (Box 24)
    - SI: General Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 24)
    - SI council, Cairo, Egypt, 1990 May 22-23 (Box 24)
    - SI Women Meeting in Geneva, 1989 November (Box 24)
    - SI Congress Publicity, 1972 (Box 24)
    - SI: Council Conference, 1967 November 19 (Box 24)
    - SI: Congress, Helsinki, 1971-1972 (Box 24)
    - SI: Council, Bonn, 1986, October, 16-17, (three folders) (Box 24)
    - SI: Appeal on Disarmament, 1984 March 17 (Box 24)